WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
Sir? This is her.
The girl who tells fortunes?
They're doing a magic spell
to make her win a race.
The horse's name's Monaghan Boy.
Kempton, three o'clock, Monday.
You ladies have a bet yourselves
but don't tell anyone else.
"And Abraham made his home in a cave,
"but it was good
"because God resided there with him.
"You see, children, God does not care
"if you live in a slum
or in a mansion.
"God does not care
if you are rich or you are poor.
"You are still God's..."
Morning, sir.
Morning, Mr Shelby.
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.
Come on, lad. Morning, sir.
Morning, Mr Shelby.
Come on, hurry up!
Finn?
Arthur's mad as hell.
What does a ten-year-old
know about hell, eh?
I'm 11 Sunday.
Place your bets here now
for the 2:30 at Kempton.
Down to fours...
OK, girls and boys,
you want to push that now, mate.
Thanks very much.
2-1, get your bets in now.
What d'you say? We've got Sovereign,
he's an old favourite, 4-1.
Tommy. Tommy!
Tommy, look at the book. Just look.
Tommy! All on Monaghan Boy.
Good work, John.
Tommy! Get in here, now!
That'll be six pennies, Nipper.
That's ten bob you'll see for that.
You was seen doing the powder trick
down at Garrison Court.
Times are hard.
People need a reason to lay a bet.
There was a Chinese.
The washer women say she's a witch.
It helps them believe.
We don't mess with Chinese.
Look at the book...
Chinese have cutters of their own.
We agreed, Arthur.
I'm taking charge
of drumming up new money.
What if Monaghan Boy wins, Tommy?
You fixing races now?
Do you have permission from Billy
Kimber to be fixing races, hm?
Then what's got into you?
You think we can take on
the Chinese and Billy Kimber.
Billy's got a bloody army!
I think... Arthur. That's what I do.
I think...
so that you don't have to.
There's news from Belfast.
Down from tens over eights...
I'm calling a family council
tonight at eight o'clock.
I want all of us there.
You hear me?!
There's trouble coming.
All right, shut up now. Shut up.
Comrades...
we're here today to take
a vote on strike action. MEN: Yes!
But before we have a show
of hands for that...
let's have a show of hands
from all those who fought in France,
all those who stood side-by-side
with your comrades
and watched your comrades fall.
Raise your hands.
The blood shed on Flanders fields,
the sweat of YOUR brows!
Who reaps the rewards?
No.
No!
- Who, then? Do they stand among us?
- No!
Or do they sit at home, comfortable,
with a full belly
while you scrape to find enough to
put shoes on your children's feet!
Yes!
And what is the reward they offer
you for your sacrifices made?
A fucking cut in your wages!
THAT is your reward!
Raise a hand, all those
who want to strike!
Yeah!
On the house, Mr Shelby.
I'll take a mild. Right.
Cheers, Thomas.
Good health to you.
The crown of a prince.
Soon to be King, I'd bet.
You don't bet.
No, but these past few days
I've been speculating.
About what?
One of my Union comrades
has a sister,
works in the telegraph office
at the BSA factory.
She says over the past week
they've had messages
coming up from London to the brass -
from Winston Churchill himself.
Something about a robbery.
"A robbery of national
significance", it said.
She found the list of names
left on the telegraph machine.
And on that list was your name
and my name together.
What kind of a list would have
the name of a Communist and the name
of a bookmaker side-by-side?
Perhaps it's a list of men
who give false hope to the poor.
The only difference
between you and me, Freddie,
is that sometimes...
my horses stand a chance of winning.
You know, there are days
when I hear about the cuttings
and beatings that I really wish I'd
let you take that bullet in France.
Believe me, there are nights
I wish you had.
They're going to get me!
On three. One, two, three, down!
Breathe, Danny, breathe!
They're going to kill me!
Danny!
Danny! Danny, you're home.
We're all home in England.
You're not in France.
You're not an artillery shell,
Danny, you're a man. Eh?
You're not a whizz bang.
You're a human being, Danny.
You're all right, you're all right,
you're all right.
Up! Up!
It's all right, it's all right.
Oh, hell. Did I do it again?
You did it again, Danny.
Got to stop doing this, man.
It's all right.
Oh, God, Mr Shelby, I'm sorry...
It's all right. You go home
to your wife now, Danny.
Try and get all that smoke
and mud out of your head, eh.
Yes, Mr Shelby. I'm sorry.
Go on.
Mr Shelby, you have to do
something about him.
Damn right, Harry.
You pay the Peaky Blinders
a lot of money for protection.
You're the law around here now,
Tommy, aren't you?
Maybe you should put a bullet
in Danny Whizz Bang's head
like they do with mad horses.
Maybe you'll have to put a bullet
in my head someday, too.
Bring the bill to the Peaky
Blinders. We'll take care of this.
Look at the gun.
Recognise it?
Oof!
Get up off your arse,
you mumping pig!
Aunt Pol! What the fuck
d'you do that for?!
Finn was playing with this this
afternoon by the cut. It was loaded.
He nearly blew Ada's tits off.
It must've fell out of my pocket.
He said he found it on the sideboard
of the betting shop...
with bullets in it.
Ma... I must've been drunk.
When are you not drunk?
Look, Aunt Pol, I'm sorry.
I'm... I'm sorry.
We'll keep this between ourselves
if you swear not to leave guns
lying around.
Look, I know having four kids
without a woman is hard.
But my boot's harder.
Now, come on, we're late.
'Right,
'I've called this family meeting
because I've got some
very important news.'
Scudboat and Lovelock got back
from Belfast last night.
They were buying a stallion
to cover their mares.
They were in a pub
on the Shankhill Road yesterday,
and in that pub,
there was a copper...
handing out these.
"If you're over five feet
and can fight, come to Birmingham."
They're recruiting Protestant
Irishmen to come over here
as Specials.
To do what?
To clean up the city, Ada.
He's a Chief Inspector.
The last four years, he's been
clearing the IRA out of Belfast.
How do you know so bloody much?
Cos I asked the coppers
on our payroll.
And why didn't you tell me?
I'm telling you.
So why are they sending him
to Birmingham?
Well, there's been all these
bloody strikes at the BSA...
and the Austin works lately.
Now the papers are talking
about sedition.
And revolution.
I reckon it's Communists he's after.
So this copper's going to
leave us alone, right?
There are Irishmen in Green Lanes
who left Belfast to get away
from him.
They say Catholic men who crossed
him used to disappear in the night.
Yeah, but we ain't IRA.
We bloody fought for the King.
Anyway, we're Peaky Blinders.
We're not scared of coppers.
He's right. If they come for us,
we'll cut them a smile each.
So, Arthur...
is that it?
What do you think, Aunt Pol?
This family does everything open.
You've nothing more to say
to this meeting, Thomas?
No.
Nothing that's women's business.
This whole bloody enterprise
was women's business
while you boys were away at war.
What's changed?
We came back.
And the Lord will smite the unholy
when the great judgment comes.
And judgment is coming, my friends.
Judgment is coming
to this wicked city.
And your wickedness and your
fornication will be revealed.
You cannot hide from the Creator.
You cannot hide from the Almighty
Himself. The Creator sees all.
You cannot hide
from the true and living God...
Get off with yer!
Fuck off!
That's it, I don't go any further.
I have ten minutes.
What do you want?
An explanation.
I've always been able to tell when
you're hiding something.
People round here talk.
Some of them work at the BSA.
I've been talking to the wives
of factory hands.
Detectives have been asking questions
in the proofing shops.
Nothing happens in that factory
without you knowing about it.
Speak.
God and Aunt Polly are listening.
It was meant to be routine.
I had a buyer in London
for some... motorcycles.
I asked my men to steal me four
bikes with petrol engines.
I'm guessing my men were drunk.
There's a still inside the factory
makes tram-line gin.
They picked up the wrong
fucking crate.
The boys dropped it at Charlie
Strong's yard as agreed.
They must've taken it from
the proofing bay
instead of the export bay.
Holy sweet baby of Mary!
Inside we found 25 Lewis
machine guns,
10,000 rounds of ammunition,
50 semi-automatic rifles,
200 pistols with shells.
Jesus, Tommy!
All bound for Libya.
Sitting right there in Charlie
Strong's yard.
Tell me you threw them in the cut.
We put 'em in the stables,
out of the rain.
The guns hadn't been greased yet.
So that's why they sent a copper
from Belfast.
Maybe, maybe not.
Thomas, you're a bookmaker,
a robber, a fighting man,
you're not a fool.
You sell those guns to anyone who
has use to 'em, you will hang!
Dump them somewhere the police
can find them.
Maybe if they know they haven't
fallen into the wrong hands
this might blow over.
Tell Charlie to dump them tonight.
No. He won't move contraband
under a full moon.
Three days until it wanes.
Then you'll do the right thing?
You have your mother's common sense,
but your father's devilment.
I see them fighting.
Let your mother win.
I got tickets for the Penny Crush.
They're showing a Tom Mix picture.
I'm not in the mood for the pictures
tonight, Ada.
Well, I'm not doing it here again.
I got covered in mud last time.
Let's just walk a bit.
If we go down as far as Greet,
we could go to a pub.
Your brothers have friends in Greet.
They have friends everywhere.
We'd have to walk to London.
I'm with you because you're the only
man round here not scared of them.
Oh, I'm scared of them all right.
But you love me more than
you fear them, right?
I don't want to be
always sneaking about.
Soon, we'll tell them. When?
How did the family meeting go?
Usual. There's a new copper coming.
I heard.
Hmm. And Tommy says he's after
the likes of you.
So maybe you should burn your books
and stop making speeches.
Oh, my Ada.
The only princess of the royal
family of the Kingdom of Small Heath.
I'm just a poor communist frog
with a big mouth.
Give me a kiss, Princess Ada.
SHE LAUGHS
I'm here about the job as a barmaid.
Are you mad? Am I what?
Do you know about this place?
I saw it in an advertisement.
Job's been filled.
It was in yesterday's paper.
Believe me, love,
I'm doing you a favour.
I'm not asking for favours,
I'm asking for employment.
You're too... nice.
How would you know? And too pretty.
They'd have you up against a wall.
I have experience and references.
What part of Ireland are you from?
Galway. Ah!
I worked in Dublin.
Me mother was from Galway.
You're too pretty.
Watch.
And listen.
♪ I wish I was in Carrickfergus
♪ Only for nights in Ballygrand
♪ I would swim over
the deepest ocean
♪ The deepest ocean
my love to find
♪ My boyhood friends
and my own relations
♪ Have all passed on now
like the melting snow. ♪
In Ireland my singing made them cry
and stopped them fighting.
Well, I hope you know
a lot of songs.
Babies...
discarded... with the fish bones
and eggshells.
Girls, 11 years old...
pierced and punctured by old men
for thruppence a time!
Rutted upon like animals!
Degradation.
Fathers with their daughters,
brothers and sisters sharing beds.
Beggars and thieves left to run
in the streets.
And astride the whole stinking
pile of wounds and rotten flesh...
your masters!
The men who you touch your cap to.
The Peaky Blinders!
The vicious... merciless gangs
who blind those that see and cut out
the tongues of those who talk.
You are worse than them!
Those of you who have taken their
bribes these years since the war,
those of you who look the other way,
you... are worse than them!
God damn you for soiling
your uniforms!
And then... there are the IRA Fenians
and the Communists.
Blacker hearts still.
They feed on the puss of all this
corruption like maggots in a corpse.
And like maggots, if left to swell
they will eventually swarm like flies
and spread their rotten philosophy
across the country
and across the world!
Those then... are our enemies!
A three-headed beast.
It is my job to decapitate each one
and by God I will do it!
I don't trust any of yous
until you earn my trust!
And that takes some earning.
These are the new men
who will bolster your ranks.
Good men...
from God-fearing families.
By the time the sun sets, they will
be sworn in and in uniform.
And by sunrise tomorrow,
they will be on the streets.
God help those who stand in our way!
Sorry, Mr Shelby.
Right. Move out of the way for Mr
Shelby. Mr Shelby. This way.
You see, ladies,
when you're out with a Blinder,
you don't have to queue.
Right... I want a blow job
off both of you
before they let
the ordinary people in.
Away you go. Take your hat off.
What the fuck?!
Who the fuck are you?!
I'm Arthur-fucking-Shelby!
Arthur Shelby.
Lead pack dog of the Peaky Blinders.
Look at me.
Bastard!
Your uniform?
Terrifying, I'm sure.
Did he have a gun? No gun. A knife
in his sock, cosh in his belt.
Now, Mr Shelby...
I want you to see this as me
introducing myself to you.
Understand?
In all the world the only thing
that interests me is the truth.
So...
what do you know about the robbery?
What robbery?
I will ask you again.
What do you know... about
the robbery?
I swear to God, I don't know
what you're talking about.
What fucking robbery?
Argh!
Aye, after 35 years of dealing
with animals like you,
I can tell just by sniffing the
air... whether or not you're lying.
I'm not fucking lying!
All right? I'm not fucking lying!
I know.
I see nothing of interest behind
the blood in your eyes.
And no blood in your veins
that could carry... even a trace
of cunning or guile.
But understand this.
It is well within my power to have
you and the rest of your scum family
face down in the canal
before the year is out.
On the other hand...
we can help each other.
Is it always this busy on a daytime?
No. These boys are on their way
to St Andrews.
To pray? That'll be the day.
St Andrews is a football ground.
The Blues are playing.
That's the forward line there.
And that's the goalie,
believe it or not. Hello!
I need a bottle of rum.
Grace, whatever it is,
it's on the house.
A whole bottle? Yeah.
White or dark rum? Don't care.
Right, lads, what'll it be? Two?
Thank you.
Harry said it's on the house.
Are you a whore?
Cos if you're not,
you're in the wrong place.
He's one of them
you warned me about?
Look, Grace, you're a friendly girl
but be careful.
If I say something's on the house,
then say nothing
to whoever you're serving.
If they decide that they want you,
then there's nothing
anybody could do about it.
Lucky for you, since he got back
from France, Tommy doesn't want
anybody at all.
Yes, lads?
John, wipe the blood out of his eye.
Since when did you give orders?
I'm a trained nurse. Don't make me
laugh, it hurts me face.
I bloody am! You went to one
first-aid class in the church hall
and got thrown out for giggling.
Not before I learnt how to stop
somebody from choking.
I'm not bloody choking, am I?
You will be when I wrap this cloth
round your neck.
Let me see him.
All right, have this.
Give me that.
You're all right.
He said Mr Churchill
sent him to Birmingham.
National interest, he said.
Something about a robbery.
He said he wants us to help him.
We don't help coppers.
He knew all about our war records.
He said we're patriots... like him.
He wants us to be his eyes and ears.
I said...
I said we'd have a family meeting
and take a vote.
Well, why not? Hmm? We've no truck
with Fenians or communists.
What's wrong with you?
What the fuck is wrong
with him lately?!
If I knew, I'd buy the cure
from Compton's Chemists.
♪ I am just a young girl
♪ I have just come over
♪ Over from the country
where they do things big
♪ And amongst the boys
♪ I've got myself a lover
♪ And since I have a lover
♪ I don't care a fig
♪ The boy I love
is up in the gallery
♪ The boy I love is...
♪ ..looking at me
♪ Can't you see him standing there
♪ Waving his handkerchief
♪ As merry as a robin
that sings on the tree. ♪
We haven't had singing
in here since the war.
Why do you think that is, Harry?
So did Arthur say what kind of deal
this new copper offered him?
God! The second your balls are empty
it's back onto politics.
What did Tommy say?
He didn't say anything.
You know what he's like.
Yeah, I know what he's like.
He likes to take his fights
onto the mud.
Doesn't like to stand and wait.
You know what he'd do
if he found out about us.
He could try.
Sometimes, it's like you're with me
just to show you can.
One day me and Tommy will be
on the same side again.
Tommy...! Aargh.
Hey, what you do?
We're closed. Go home.
Go home, crazy man.
I said go home, crazy man!
I said go home.
Fix bayonets!!!
Secretary of State,
this is Chief Inspector Campbell.
Mr Churchill, sir, may I say what
a great honour it is to meet you.
Bit of a whistle stop tour.
Love the hat, by the way.
Thank you. It's beaver.
So, how are you settling in?
I have set up a command network.
I have agents in place
across the city
who will act as my eyes and ears.
And I have begun to interrogate
suspects vigorously.
You were in Belfast. I understand
you broke a few Fenian hearts.
A rat's nest, sir.
So who do you think stole the guns?
Fenians or Communists?
If it is IRA Fenians, I will
find them and find the guns.
If it is Communists, I will find them
and find the guns.
If it is common criminals,
I will find them and find the guns.
To me there are no distinction
between any of the above.
We chose you
because you are effective.
But remember this, Mr Campbell.
This is England, not Belfast.
Bodies thrown in the rivers,
wash up in the papers here.
We must keep the existence of these
stolen guns out of the news
otherwise we will simply be
advertising them for sale.
If there are bodies to be buried,
dig holes and dig them deep.
I want everything accounted for
down to the last bullet.
Uncle Charlie, a word.
They are aboard. There's no moon.
We can take them out to the turning
point beyond Gas Street
and leave them on the bank.
They'll be found by railway men
first thing.
Is that agreement?
I changed my mind.
You what?
I have an alternative strategy.
Tell Curly to take her out
to the old tobacco wharf.
There's a lock up mooring
we used to keep cigarettes.
He knows it.
When the boat leaves your yard,
it's no longer your concern.
Have you lost your fucking mind?
Have you not seen the streets?
They've sent a fucking army
to find these things...
That's right.
They've shown their hand...
Their hand?
If they want them back this bad,
they'll have to pay.
That's the way of the world.
Fortune drops something
valuable in your lap,
You don't just dump it
on the bank of the cut.
You're blood, Tommy.
I've always looked out for you
like a dad.
You're going to bring holy hell
down on your head.
This copper takes no prisoners.
I'm told he didn't serve.
Reserved occupation.
Is it another war
you're looking for, Tommy?
The tobacco wharf.
By order of the Peaky Blinders.
Are you in position?
I am, sir.
Your first impressions?
I am quite shocked at how
these people live.
Have you found anything
out that might help me?
I interrogated the head of the Peaky
Blinders. He didn't know anything.
A brute.
It strikes me that it isn't Arthur
who heads the Shelby family.
It is the younger one, Thomas.
They say he won two medals
for gallantry in the war.
You sound fascinated.
However, my opinion has not changed.
The bookmaker gangs
have other business
and the Communists are too weak
to have planned this.
I believe the guns
were taken by the IRA.
You must not let your personal
history cloud your judgment.
What history?
That the IRA murdered my father
will not affect my judgment.
If you see any guns, check the
serial numbers against that list.
Your father was the finest officer
I ever worked with.
I know he would be very,
very proud of you.
Danny, as you know, the man
you killed was Italian.
And those two men
over there are his brothers.
If I let the Italians do this,
Danny,
they'll cut off your manhood
and let you drain.
That's how those bastards do things.
So, to stop a war breaking
out between us and the Italians...
and to save you from
their barbarity...
I said I would
dispatch you myself.
They are here to witness.
I died over there anyway, Tommy.
I left my fucking brains in the mud.
You have any last requests, comrade?
You'll look out for my Rosie
and my boys?
See they get apprenticeships.
At the BSA factory or the Austin.
They'll make foremen.
I know they will.
Just ordinary...
Just ordinary men.
And they won't get told
to do this shit...
This shit... This shit
that we got told to do.
I suppose I ought to pray now.
Those fucking guns blew God
right out of my head.
Is that boat for me?
We have to get your body out
of the city, Danny.
This new copper, you know...
Don't bury me anywhere
where there's mud. OK?
Promise me.
Bury me on a hill
and tell Rosie where.
You were a good man
and a good soldier.
Yes, Sergeant Major.
In the bleak midwinter.
GUNSHOT
Where are you?
It bloody won!
Monaghan Boy bloody won!
Yeah. It won.
And word will spread.
So next time we do the powder trick
it won't just be The Garrison
that'll bet on the horse,
it'll be the whole of Small Heath.
And you know what?
The horse will win again.
And the third time we do it
we'll have the whole of Birmingham
betting on it.
A thousand quid bet
on the magic horse.
And that time, when we are ready,
the horse will lose.
Think about it.
You OK, Danny?
I'm still in shock.
You sure this isn't heaven?
If it was heaven,
what would I be doing here?
Tommy wanted you to think
it was real
to try and knock some
sense into you.
A shell full of sheep brains
hurts pretty bad.
It was meant to.
So where are you taking me?
London.
Tommy has a little job for you.
Give you chance to say thanks.
You're a Peaky Blinder now, Danny.
A bad week.
There was no moon last night.
I checked.
Did you do the right thing?
Yes, I did the right thing.
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.